<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <PRFHelp>Help</PRFHelp>
  <PRFHelpDesc>View help for this item.</PRFHelpDesc>
  <PRFViewOrdo>Ordo Historia: {0}</PRFViewOrdo>

  <PRF_DeepQuarry_HelpText>The deep quarry is used for extraction of random mineral resources from underground, and produces a resource on average once every 6 hours. It functions like a colonist miner would - it randomly selects a rock or compacted resource (Granite, compacted steel) according to commonality and returns its mined products. Hence, rock chunks are the most common products of deep quarries, followed by the various commonalities of other resources.</PRF_DeepQuarry_HelpText>
  <Shearer_HelpText>Animal harvesters automatically harvest animals when they come near the vicinity of the building. Store food at those stations to coerce animals to come to the stations so they can be harvested.</Shearer_HelpText>
  <Milker_HelpText>Animal harvesters automatically harvest animals when they come near the vicinity of the building. Store food at those stations to coerce animals to come to the stations so they can be harvested.</Milker_HelpText>
  <GenericAnimalHarvester_HelpText>Animal harvesters automatically harvest animals when they come near the vicinity of the building. Store food at those stations to coerce animals to come to the stations so they can be harvested.</GenericAnimalHarvester_HelpText>
  <PaperclipFactory_HelpText>The paperclip factory doesn't just take in steel - it can make paperclips from any item by manipulating its subatomic structure. The number of paperclips produced is equivalent to 1/4 of the combined mass of the ingredients.</PaperclipFactory_HelpText>
  <PaperclipFactory_OrdoText><![CDATA[<b>Ordo Historia Standardization Archive - OHS 15616 - A paperclip used as feedstock for a standard atomic 3d printing device(OHS 6011)</b>
Section 1.1 - Physical properties
- A single paperclip must weigh 1.0 ± 1*10^-8 grams.
- It can be made out of any form of matter, including exotic matter(OHS 11279) such as Dalekanium, Unobtainium or Vibranium; however, the end product has to exhibit the properties of a metal such that it is pliable, ductile and malleable.
- Paperclips must have a positive real mass.
- For instructions about how to manufacture a paperclip, see the Lantz-Foddy method for producing paperclips from matter(OHS 58281)
- Paperclips mus<color=red><b>[TRANSMISSION ABORTED - POTENTIAL SECURITY BREACH DETECTED]</b></color>
]]>  </PaperclipFactory_OrdoText>
  <UniversalAssembler_HelpText>To get any assembler building set up, go to its "Bills" tab and add the bills you want in order. Then configure its output so that the yellow cell is where you want the products to go. Finally, place the required ingredients around it (if you're using a smart hopper, remember to check "toggle allow forbidden"), and give it power.\n\nTo feed recipes into this assembler, build a recipe database and place it next to the work table you want to copy bills from(See the recipe database help for additional instructions). Once finished with the import(s), reinstall it near this building.</UniversalAssembler_HelpText>
  <MachineLearningAssembler_HelpText>This assembler is special in that it gets faster at its recipes the more it works on them. Over time, however, this skill also decays exponentially.\n\nTo get any assembler building set up, go to its "Bills" tab and add the bills you want in order. Then configure its output so that the yellow cell is where you want the products to go. Finally, place the required ingredients around it (if you're using a smart hopper, remember to check "toggle allow forbidden"), and give it power.\n\nTo feed recipes into this assembler, build a recipe database and place it next to the work table you want to copy bills from. See the help for the recipe database for additional instructions. Once finished with the import(s), reinstall it near this building.</MachineLearningAssembler_HelpText>
  <PRFFermentingBarrel_HelpText>To get this building set up, go to the “Bills” tab and aldd the bills you want in order. Then configure the output so that the yellow cell is where you want the beer to be placed after fermentation. Finally, place wort around it (if you are using a smart hopper, remember to check toggle “allow forbidden”), and give it power.</PRFFermentingBarrel_HelpText>
  <PRF_Recycler_HelpText>This machine can recycle crushing and sorting almost any apperal and weapon back to useable raw resources in a cost of some lost materials. Remember to clear output so new stuff can be spit out.</PRF_Recycler_HelpText>
  <SelfPrepper_HelpText>This is a Automatic food prepping table made originally for VGP Gourmet but will be featured in other mods and maybe vanilla too. input raw food and get out ingredient to make food</SelfPrepper_HelpText>
  <MeatGrinder_HelpText>This Dangerous looking machine works by putting in dead animals, and out will come meat, hide and any other part? Remove fast from output to avoid clogging, as only one item can output at time.</MeatGrinder_HelpText>
  <SelfCooker_HelpText>To get any assembler building set up, go to its "Bills" tab and add the bills you want in order. Then configure its output so that the yellow cell is where you want the products to go. Finally, place the required ingredients around it (if you're using a smart hopper, remember to check "toggle allow forbidden"), and give it power.</SelfCooker_HelpText>
  <RecipeDatabase_HelpText>To start importing recipes from a work table: Place this building near the work table, go to "Import recipe..." and select the recipe you want to import. Make sure the building actually has power.</RecipeDatabase_HelpText>
  <CultivatorTools_b18Cultivator_HelpText>The cultivator operates automatically if it is given power. It will sow and harvest crops in growing zones and output them into a nearby cell. If you also have the mod SeedsPlease installed, the cultivator requires seeds to be placed next to it for sowing to work.</CultivatorTools_b18Cultivator_HelpText>
  <CultivatorTools_b18CultivatorSun_HelpText>The cultivator operates automatically if it is given power. It will sow and harvest crops in growing zones and output them into a nearby cell. If you also have the mod SeedsPlease installed, the cultivator requires seeds to be placed next to it for sowing to work.</CultivatorTools_b18CultivatorSun_HelpText>
  <CultivatorTools_DroneCultivator_HelpText>The cultivator operates automatically if it is given power. It will sow and harvest crops in growing zones and output them into ground, use a growzone puller to collect. If you also have the mod SeedsPlease installed, the cultivator requires seeds to be placed next to it for sowing to work.</CultivatorTools_DroneCultivator_HelpText>
  <CultivatorTools_CultivatorWithLamp_HelpText>The cultivator operates automatically if it is given power. It will sow and harvest crops in growing zones and output them into ground, use a growzone puller to collect. If you also have the mod SeedsPlease installed, the cultivator requires seeds to be placed next to it for sowing to work.</CultivatorTools_CultivatorWithLamp_HelpText>
  <CultivatorTools_Sprinkler_HelpText>The sprinkler randomly boosts the growth of crops and plants by 1 hour each round. You can see which cell it is currently working at by selecting it.</CultivatorTools_Sprinkler_HelpText>
  <FuelingMachine_HelpText>The fueling machine is quite easy to use. Point the robotic arm at the building you want to fuel, place fuel next to it and give it power.</FuelingMachine_HelpText>
  <PRFPaperclipPowerGenerator_HelpText>The paperclip power generator is just like a normal power generator, except it runs off paperclips and has 2 extra features:\n1. You can adjust the fuel consumption rate to ramp up/down the power production.\n2. After unlocking "Paperclip power generator: self-improvement" in research, power production efficiency can slowly ramp up, as long as the building has fuel and is powered at all times.</PRFPaperclipPowerGenerator_HelpText>
  <AtomicReconstructor_HelpText>The atomic reconstructor turns paperclips into items. Simply fuel it up, add power, set the item you want to produce and wait. You can also make it work faster by adjusting the slider. Note that the speed is directly proportional to the square of the paperclip cost, for example if you set the speed to 2x, it will use 4x more paperclips.\n\nGenerally, items that are more expensive take longer to make, and items that are heavier cost more paperclips.\n\nNote: The atomic reconstructor cannot make any items that have to be made from a material (for example, steel longsword)</AtomicReconstructor_HelpText>
  <PRFPaperclipDuplicator_HelpText>Think of the paperclip duplicator as a bank: it stores paperclips and gives you a set interest on those paperclips. The Duplicator tab provides an interface for you to deposit/withdraw paperclips. Note that you need to provide a cargo platform as an item source for depositing/withdrawing paperclips.\n\nThe formula that is used for calculating the current paperclip amount is:\nCurrentBalance = 1.05^(DaysPassed) * InitialBalance</PRFPaperclipDuplicator_HelpText>
  <PRFStorageUnitIOPort_HelpText>To configure the storage unit I/O port, set the mode (input or output), and the unit you want to connect to. If you choose output, remember to also select the item that you want to pull.</PRFStorageUnitIOPort_HelpText>
  <SAL_SmartHopper_HelpText>The smart hopper pulls in nearby items onto itself. If you place it near an assembler, remember to enable the assembler's "toggle allow forbidden" option.</SAL_SmartHopper_HelpText>
  <StockpileCrate_HelpText>To output to crates and cargo platforms with the "Industrial Rollers" mod, remember to use a roller pusher at the end.</StockpileCrate_HelpText>
  <StockpileCrateReinforced_HelpText>To output to crates and cargo platforms with the "Industrial Rollers" mod, remember to use a roller pusher at the end.</StockpileCrateReinforced_HelpText>
  <PRFCargoPlatform_HelpText>The cargo platform functions like any other storage building, but all items put inside are moved to the middle cell, allowing for virtually infinite storage capacity.\n\nTo prevent considerable lag in heavily used cargo platforms, the item readout in the "Items" tab only displays the first 500 items. You can, however, search for the item you want using the search bar.\n\nNOTE: To output to crates and cargo platforms with the "Industrial Rollers" mod, remember to use a roller pusher at the end.</PRFCargoPlatform_HelpText>
  <IndustrialStorageUnit_HelpText>The Industrial Storage Unit functions like any other storage building, but all items put inside are moved to the middle cell, allowing for 999 stacks capacity.\n\nTo prevent considerable lag in heavily used cargo platforms, the item readout in the "Items" tab only displays the first 500 items. You can, however, search for the item you want using the search bar.\n\nNOTE: To output to crates and cargo platforms with the "Industrial Rollers" mod, remember to use a roller pusher at the end.</IndustrialStorageUnit_HelpText>
  <Lighting_FloorLampArrow_HelpText>Signs to indicate what direction things going or just decorate your room? Someone spilled glowy goo from bugs while making it so it have a slight glow to it</Lighting_FloorLampArrow_HelpText>
  <Lighting_RedFloorLampArrow_HelpText>Signs to indicate what direction things going or just decorate your room? Someone spilled glowy goo from bugs while making it so it have a slight glow to it</Lighting_RedFloorLampArrow_HelpText>
  <Lighting_GreenFloorLampArrow_HelpText>Signs to indicate what direction things going or just decorate your room? Someone spilled glowy goo from bugs while making it so it have a slight glow to it</Lighting_GreenFloorLampArrow_HelpText>
  <Lighting_FloorLampX_HelpText>Signs to indicate what direction things going or just decorate your room? Someone spilled glowy goo from bugs while making it so it have a slight glow to it</Lighting_FloorLampX_HelpText>
  <Building_AutoMachineTool_Miner_HelpText>This is a Highly costumizable Miner that can be set for your need with newest spacer technolgy in your hands</Building_AutoMachineTool_Miner_HelpText>
  <Building_AutoMachineTool_Puller_HelpText>A Second Tiered Pusher That have some more options then Industrial roller version, this can properly connect if IR cant.</Building_AutoMachineTool_Puller_HelpText>
  <Building_AutoMachineTool_Puller_Wall_HelpText>This is walled version of the Second Tiered Pusher That have some more options then Industrial roller version, this can properly connect if IR cant.</Building_AutoMachineTool_Puller_Wall_HelpText>
  <Building_AutoMachineTool_Slaughterhouse_HelpText>A slaughter house that can manage and auto kill animals if they exceed a specified number, age or gender. good in combination with "Auto Meat Grinder" and "Animal stations"</Building_AutoMachineTool_Slaughterhouse_HelpText>

  <!--   <xxx_HelpText></xxx_HelpText>   -->

</LanguageData>