<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Project RimFactory Revived</name>
  <author>zymex</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>spdskatr.projectrimfactory</packageId>
  <url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=30813.0</url>
  <description>
WIP - Unstable - Beta
Please know by using this mod theres a risk of things being removed or break.
Until a stable release are ready.

This mod adds:
This mod is together with Industrial Rollers an Awesome way to automate and create factories and such in Rimworld.
I always loved those 2 mods, and now i have the chance to update one of them

- 3 Animal Stations to milk, shear, and harvest
- 3 Cultivators to plant and harvest your crops and make them grow faster
- 5 Auto-Assemblers that will auto craft, cook stuff for you
- 1 deep drilling machine that will mine random blocks for you
and more...
this might change but list from original mod.

Disclaimer
This was my Favorite mod in B18 and B19 and there never really came a 1.0 or 1.1
So i was looking into updating it, since Spdskatr properbly wont come back.
i saw AbnerChen made asemblies update and created a PR but Spdskatr didnt update.

I used this in combination with my own work and original to update to 1.1
I hope this mod can be a Continuation of Spdskatr excellent mod.
i dont want credit, i really just want my favorite mod back to rimworld 1.1 standard

I sadly have no C# skills so can't build upon assemblies, so if some one wanna take over or colab feel free to contact me.


New in this version:
- Patch for Industrial Rollers (clean up menus)
- Changed Menu name to Industrial to merge menus with Industrial Rollers
- Grouped items in Menu
- Architech menu icon (support)
- updated assemblies by AbnerChen
- Working with AutoSort in 1.1
- Balanced research and cost of Deep Drilling.
- New textures aniamal station,
- Updated texture for storage crates by Chicken Plucker(more will come)
- Included Rest of SS bigger battieries instead of just 2.
- Research AI bench now only 3x1 instead of 5x2
- Included PRF - Storage into Core again.
- Moved PaperClips research out of core into Insanity (not out yet)

Any bugs, suggestion or other are VERY welcome as i cant test i all myself.

Question
Do you want all in one mod? or 4 seprate mods like PFR 1.0 did (updated for now)
-Core (this one)
-Storage (In core now)
-Drones (will be seprate later)
-Insanity (will be seprate later, maybe.... seems like no one want it)

- Should i Remove stuffed from animal stations and group them?
- If yes what matrial shall it be made off?


Credits:
assemblies for 1.1: AbnerChen
Data disk and tape player textures by totobrother
Wood crate texture: Chicken Plucker 2 years ago and updated 2020!
Robotic arm texture: Shotgunfrenzy
Drone texture: Xen
X/Y/Z-Composite + drone station texture: Scythe
Spdskatr - Rimfactory original! see: https://github.com/spdskatr/ProjectRimFactory

Translaters: (might need update after release)
Russian: Natsu_Zirok, Chinese Simplified: Dango998, Chinese Traditional: AbnerChen
  </description>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>historic.IndustrialRollers</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <incompatibleWith>
    <li>Spdskatr.ssBiggerBatteries</li>
  </incompatibleWith>
</ModMetaData>
